(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
僕たちは配信アプリ、ホロキャスで活動する配信者。
We are streamers who are active on the streaming app, HoloCas.
突然画面に吸い込まれて、アプリと繋がる謎の世界、ホロキャス界に来ちゃった。
Suddenly, we were sucked into the screen and ended up in the HoloCas World—a mysterious realm connected to the app.
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象、夢落ちが起こっていた。
In that world, a phenomenon called 'Dreamfall' was occurring, where the souls of people suffering in reality turned into monsters.
怪物コラプサーを倒して、みんなの魂を取り戻さないと。
We have to defeat the monster Corruptors and take back everyone's souls.
そうして、魔法少女に変身して、戦うことになった。
And so, we ended up transforming into magical girls to fight.
みんなの心を助けて、夢を応援する！
Saving everyone's hearts and supporting their dreams!
それが...
That is...
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
Magical Girl HoloWitch!
今日はスペシャルハロウィンステージ！
Today is the Special Halloween Stage!
ホロキャスの人気配信者が多数出演！
Many popular HoloCas streamers will be performing!
さらに、今をときめく超人気歌手のカノンさんも参加する、超、超豪華イベント！
What's more, the incredibly popular singer Kanon will be joining us in this super, super extravagant event!
で、その超豪華イベントのオープニングアクトをうちら6人が担当することになって、
So, the six of us were put in charge of the opening act for this super extravagant event,
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着て、ドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかなーって。
and I thought it'd be cool if we all wore our HoloWitch outfits and really livened things up with a bang.
でもいいのかな？魔法とか、妖精とか、一応内緒なんだけど。
But is that okay? Magic and fairies are supposed to be a secret, you know.
今日はハロウィンだから、仮装ってことにすれば、なんとかなるなる！
Since it's Halloween today, we can just say it's cosplay, so it'll work out somehow!
そうそう。
Exactly.
って、そろそろ準備した方が良くない？
Wait, shouldn't we start getting ready soon?
そうだね。
You're right.
じゃ、気合入れていきますか！
Then, let's get fired up and go for it!
トリック・オア...
Trick or...
...トリート！
...Treat!
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中、
Obsessed, obsessed, obsessed,
足りないでしょ？
It's not enough, is it?
こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Come over here and let's play
ねこちゅーシンドローム
Nekochu Syndrome
イライライライライラして
Feeling irritated, irritated, irritated...
楽しくいられぬために、現況
In this current situation where we can't stay happy
イライライライライラしてたら
If you keep feeling irritated like that
魂抜ける、もったいない！
Your soul will slip away—what a waste!
どうしたら喜んでくれるかな、さぁ。
How can I make you happy? Let's see.
思いついては即行動、スマイルハンター！
Acting as soon as I think of it—Smile Hunter!
お望み君のツボ、ピンポイント撃ち抜いちゃお、絶好
I'll hit your sweet spot with pinpoint precision, perfect!
魔法だもん、愛の呪文、ホロキャスと、コンサート！
It's magic, a spell of love! HoloCas and concert!
まだまだ仕掛けちゃえ！
I've got even more tricks up my sleeve!
あっという間に捕まえた！
Caught you in a flash!
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中シンドローム
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu Syndrome
いたずらからのハピネス
Happiness coming from a prank
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中したら
When you're obsessed, obsessed, obsessed
ギュってね、爆死です、スマイルに！
With a squeeze, I'm dying of joy from your smile!
年中無休カーニバル、好きが重なれば
A year-round carnival, when our 'likes' pile up
年中無休カーニバル、お祭り
A year-round carnival, a festival
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中足りない
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu, it's not enough
こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Come over here and let's play
とに角に、信じちゃえ、ほらね！
Anyway, just believe in it, see!
未来は完璧、アドレナリン飛ば飛ばさせちゃうんです
The future is perfect, I'll make your adrenaline soar
降伏したらみんなが...
Once you surrender, everyone...
ちょっと待って、私の出番！
Wait a minute, it's my turn!
どういうこと！？
What do you mean!?
もうハチャメチャだー！
It's a total mess now!
案じ真似違っても、同じ道行く
Even if our paths look different, we're going the same way
響き合って集まれば、詰まり最強じゃん！
When we resonate and gather, we're basically the strongest!
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中シンドローム
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu Syndrome
高鳴りすぎて白熱
Hearts racing so fast, we're glowing white-hot
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中、至宝、極上のウィンク！
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu treasure—the ultimate wink!
異世界から見せたいよ、目一杯の愛
I want to show you my full love from another world
こんなにも近くにいるよ！
I'm standing right here, so close!
年中無休で笑いたい、君と笑いあいたいな
I want to laugh year-round, I want to laugh with you
やよやよよし、していたら、いつのまにか救われちゃう
If I keep doing this, before you know it, you'll be saved
幸せすぎて困っちゃう、浮かべたら花盛り！
So happy it's a problem, blossoming with joy!
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中シンドローム
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu Syndrome
いたずらからのハピネス
Happiness coming from a prank
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中したら
When you're obsessed, obsessed, obsessed
ギュってね、爆死です、スマイルに！
With a squeeze, I'm dying of joy from your smile!
年中無休カーニバル、好きが重なれば
A year-round carnival, when our 'likes' pile up
年中無休カーニバル、お祭り
A year-round carnival, a festival
ねっ中、ねっ中、ねっ中足りない
Netchu, Netchu, Netchu, it's not enough
こっちおいで遊ぼうよ
Come over here and let's play
とに角に、信じちゃえ、ほらね！
Anyway, just believe in it, see!
魔法少女ホロウィッチ！ THE STAGE TRICK or MAGIC!
Magical Girl holoWitches! THE STAGE ~TRICK or MAGIC!~
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or Treat!
みんな、盛り上がってるー！？
Everyone, are you excited?!
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト、どうだったー！？
How was the holoWitches' opening act?!
ここからもっと、もっと盛り上げていくのら！
We're going to hype things up even more from here!
みんなで一緒に楽しもうね！
Let's all enjoy it together!
今日は我々ホロキャスの配信者だけじゃなく、
Today, we're joined by more than just us HoloCas streamers;
あの超人気歌手、カノンさんがゲストで来てくださってまーす！
the super popular singer Kanon-san is here as a guest!
カノンさん、どうぞー！
Please welcome Kanon-san!
トリック・オア・トリート。
Trick or Treat.
みんな、今日は最後までよろしく。
Everyone, please enjoy yourselves until the end today.
ひやー、まさか、あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるなんて！
Whoa, I can't believe we're on the same stage as Kanon-san!
いや本当、憧れですよ！
Truly, she's an idol to us!
カノンさんの歌を聞くと、すっごくパワーもらえるのら！
Listening to Kanon-san's singing gives me so much power!
そうそう！こんなに頂いちゃっていいんですか！？ってくらいね。
Right?! Like, "is it okay to receive this much?!"
うーん、めっちゃ元気出るよ！
Hmm, it's so energizing!
お？
Oh?
ありがとう。なんでもないから。
Thank you. It's nothing.
次の曲はみんなも一緒に歌ってほしいのら！
We want everyone to sing along for the next song!
君たち、遠慮しないで声出してね！声！
You guys, don't hold back, let's hear those voices! Voices!
じょいふる
作詞・作曲：水野良樹
Joyful
Lyrics/Composition: Yoshiki Mizuno
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ 冒険してみない？
Now, shall we go on an adventure?
楽しいこと始めよう
Let's start something fun
遊びたい 絶対 トトタイタイ
I want to play, definitely...
あわない じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
ポップな ベイベー
Pop baby
じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
ハッピーな ピーポー
Happy people
弱虫なんかじゃない
I'm not a coward
自信あり アイデンティティー
I have confidence in my identity
君の瞳にキスして
Kiss your eyes
笑いたい 絶対 トトタイタイ
I want to laugh, definitely...
あわない じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
陽気な ベイベー
Cheerful baby
じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
ハッピーな セイイェー
Happy say yeah
君の心はそっとギュッギュッ
Your heart gently tightens
僕の心はそっとイッスンギュッギュッ
My heart also tightens
はじけてるんじゃない？
Isn't it popping?
イッツ・じょいふる・ハッピー・ベイベー・ポップ
It's joyful happy baby pop
イェイ！
Yeah!
ドキドキしちゃうのなんでだろ
I wonder why my heart is pounding
ウキウキしちゃうのなんでだろ
I wonder why I'm feeling excited
この夢に止まるのはどんな運命なんだろう
I wonder what kind of fate it is to stop in this dream
つくしたい
I want to devote myself
じょいふるだけで終わっちゃう
It'll end with just being joyful
エブリバディ いつも終わっちゃう
Everybody, it always ends
いついつまでもこの時を
This moment forever and ever
最終形はきっと修正なしで
The final form will surely be without correction
ドゥビドゥ ドゥビドゥ ドゥビドゥドゥ
Do-be-do, do-be-do, do-be-do-do
テンポ・テンポ・ハッピー・ポップ・タイ・トタイ・トタイタイ
Tempo, tempo, happy pop, tie, to-tie, to-tie-tie
あわない じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
陽気な ベイベー
Cheerful baby
じょい と じょい と じょい
Joy and joy and joy
ハッピーな セイイェー
Happy say yeah
君の心はそっとギュッギュッ
Your heart gently tightens
僕の心はそっとイッスンギュッギュッ
My heart also tightens
はじけてるんじゃない？
Isn't it popping?
イッツ・じょいふる・ハッピー・ベイベー・ポップ
It's joyful happy baby pop
じょい！
Joy!
みんな、一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for singing along with us!
いやー、よかったね。会場がね、一体になったって感じでね。
Wow, that was great. I really felt like we were one with the crowd.
うん。
Yeah.
よかった、よかった。
It was so good, so good.
テンション上がるわー、これ。
This is really getting me pumped up.
さ、さあ次は、いよいよカノンさんに歌っていただきます！
N-Now then, up next, Kanon-san will finally be performing for us!
君、
Are you...
大丈夫？
...okay?
あ、なに？
Wait, what?
なにこれ！
What's this?!
なになに！
What's going on?!
なんなのなの？
What is it, nano?
え？
Huh?
えぇー！？
Whaaaaat?!
あわ...
Oh...
あわって...
Oh my...
まさか！
No way!
うわぁ！
Whoa!
取れないんだけど！
I can't get it off!
なにこれ！
What is this thing?!
ちょちょちょちょちょ！
Whoa whoa whoa whoa!
なになに？どういうこと？
What? What's happening?
コラプサーだ！
It's a Corrupsa!
ですよね、どう考えてもね！
Of course it is, no matter how you look at it!
コラプサー。やっぱり。
A Corrupsa. Just as I thought.
痛い痛い痛い！
Ow ow ow ow!
わりゃ！
Take that!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary, scary, scary!
えーと、こういう時は...
U-Um, in times like these...
ト、トリック・オア・トリート！
T-Trick or Treat!
何もかも違うだろ！
That's wrong in every possible way!
顔が、顔が変になってるよ！
Her face... her face is turning weird!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
出てる出てる！楽しいの素が出たな！
It's coming out! Her essence of fun is coming out!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
でも、コラプサーが出てくるってことは...
Ugh... But if the Corrupsas are appearing...
夢落ちしてる人がいるんだ、多分。
Someone must be suffering a Dream Fall, probably.
ミオ先輩！
Mio-senpai!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
ご、ごめん。うち、うち...
I-I'm sorry. I... I...
本当は、本当は...
Actually, actually...
ハロウィンのカボチャが怖くてだめなのー！
I'm just so terrified of Halloween pumpkins that I can't do anything!
ちっちゃい頃、パパがハロウィンであれ被って帰ってきて...
When I was little, my dad came home for Halloween wearing one of those...
ただいまー
I'm home!
うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって思っちゃって。
And I thought a pumpkin had eaten my daddy.
ハッピーハロウィーン！！
Happy Halloween!!
それから、
Ever since then,
どうしても、
no matter what,
ハロウィンのカボチャだけは、
Halloween pumpkins are the one thing
無理なのー！
I just can't handle!
チェンジ！
Change!
ガーディアン・アーム！
Guardian Arm!
巫女神の輪（みこがみのろった）！
Mikogami no Rotta!
キャンディー・パラソル！
Candy Parasol!
頑張りな！
Go for it!
スノーフレーク・セイバー！
Snowflake Saber!
吹切丸（ふぶきりまる）！
Fubukirimaru!
ここは任せて、ミオ。
Leave this to us, Mio.
みんな...
Everyone...
魔法、みんなに見せちゃうけど、いいよね？
We're going to show everyone our magic, okay?
うん、そんなこと言ってらんないし。
Yeah, we don't have time to worry about that now.
だよね！夢落ちした人を助ける。それが...
Right! Helping people who suffer a Dream Fall. That is...
魔法少女、ホロウィッチ！
...Magical Girl HoloWitch!
この手を差し伸べ、掴んで、握る。
Reach out this hand, seize, and hold tight.
天音のホロ、魔法少女かなた！
The Holo of Amane, Magical Girl Kanata!
みんなの願いを咲かせる祈り。
A prayer to make everyone's wishes bloom.
みこのホロ、魔法少女みこ！
The Holo of Miko, Magical Girl Miko!
甘い幸せ、お裾分け。
A helping of sweet happiness.
姫森のホロ、魔法少女ルーナ！
The Holo of Himemori, Magical Girl Luna!
きらめくお宝、ロックオン。
Sparkling treasures, locked on.
海賊のホロ、魔法少女マリン！
The Holo of the Pirate, Magical Girl Marine!
心躍らすトリックスター。
The heart-dancing trickster.
狐のホロ、魔法少女フブキ！
The Holo of the Fox, Magical Girl Fubuki!
凍りつくさなる純白の愛、
Pure white love like a frozen flower,
雪のホロ！
Snowy holo!
魔法少女ラミィ！
Magical Girl Lamy!
ホロウィッチ！
holoWitches!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
行くよ！
Here I go!
ほい、ほい、はい！
Hoi, hoi, hai!
こん！
Kon!
やめな。
Stop it.
えい！
Ei!
おいおいおい。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
ね、なんかこれ、まずくない？どんどん強くなってる。
Hey, isn't this getting bad? They're getting stronger.
みんなが奴らを倒すより、不安と恐れが膨れ上がるほうが早いみたい！
The fear and anxiety are growing faster than you can defeat them!
そんな！
No way!
うちのせい...
It's my fault...
...うちが、あんなもの怖いって思っちゃうせいで...
...because I keep thinking those things are scary...
そんなこと...
That's not...
わかってるの。
I know it.
おかしいよね、あんなのが、
It's weird, isn't it? To be...
こんな、どうしようもなく怖いなんて。
...this helplessly terrified of them.
だから、今日も我慢して、頑張ろうって、思ったのに。
That's why I thought I'd just endure it and do my best today.
でも... でもやっぱり！
But... But I just can't!
おかしくなんてないよ。
It's not weird at all.
カノンさん...
Kanon-san...
誰にだって、苦手なものがある。
Everyone has something they're not good at.
怖いもの。嫌いなもの。
Things they fear. Things they hate.
人に何でそんなものが、って言われても、
Even if people ask why you're bothered by such things,
どうしようもないことって、やっぱりあるよ。
there are just some things you can't help.
そうだよ！
That's right!
何が苦手とか、何が怖いかとかは関係なくて、
What you're bad at or what you fear doesn't matter.
大事なのは、今、ミオちゃんが辛いって思ってるかどうかだから！
What matters is whether you're hurting right now, Mio-chan!
遠慮しないで。
Don't hold back.
頼ってほしいにぇ！
I want you to lean on us!
だって、そういうのさ。
Because, you know,
うちら、お互い様じゃん！
we're all in this together!
誰かの辛さ、誰かの苦手は、他の誰かがカバーする。
When one of us hurts or struggles, the others cover for them.
お互い、そうやって、やってきたんだから！
That's how we've always made it through!
今だって！
Even now!
こんなに頑張れる！
We can fight this hard!
ホロウィッチ、コラプターは、
holoWitches, the Corruptors
夢落ちした人の恐れと不安から生まれ、
are born from the fear and anxiety of the fallen,
その心を深く沈ませてしまう。
sinking their hearts into the depths.
夢落ちって、どうしてそれを...？
The fallen? How do you know about that...?
でも、私は知ってる。
But I know this.
君たちなら、ホロウィッチなら、
If it's you, if it's the holoWitches,
辛い、苦しい、悲しい、きつい...
no matter how painful, agonizing, or sad it gets...
そんな、自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中にいても、
even in a darkness you can't escape alone,
夢を、光を届けてくれる。
you will bring forth dreams and light.
任せて！
Leave it to us!
さあ、みんな。ホロウィッチが戦ってくれる。
Now, everyone. The holoWitches are fighting for us.
では、私たちにできるのは？
So, what can we do?
そう、私たちの声で、思いで、
That's right, with our voices and our feelings,
彼女たちを応援することだ！
we must cheer them on!
いざ、トリック・オア・トリート！
Now, Trick or Treat!
仮装狂騒曲
Masquerade Rhapsody
作詞：TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.)
Lyrics: TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.)
作曲：FAKE TYPE.
Composition: FAKE TYPE.
あれよという間に飲み込まれ
Swallowed up in the blink of an eye
橙色のタイダルウェーブ やっこ やっこ
An orange tidal wave, heave-ho, heave-ho
ハンドメイドからオーダーメイドまで仕掛ける大流行
From handmade to custom-made, starting a huge craze
蜘蛛の巣から見せ物小屋まで纏めて大集合
From spider webs to sideshow tents, everyone gather 'round
添えも添えたり不遇な世界に お揃いの装束で ヘケケケケ
Adding more to this unfortunate world in matching outfits, hee-hee-hee-hee
これ見よがしの奴隷よ どおしようどれい？ 呪術的フォーメーションで ホップ ステップ トレイン
Look at these slaves, what to do, slaves? In a magical formation, hop step train
メーデーが特急から
Mayday from the express train
ジョニーをどつければ
If we wallop Johnny
チヤホヤしたりされたりがいいでしょ？ 今更じゃ物足りない義務感も
Pampering and being pampered feels good, right? Obligation isn't enough anymore
茶劇は一旦切って エブリバディ ご機嫌 エブリタイム センシティブ ティブ チグハグ お祭り騒ぎの 始まりだ
Cut the charade, everybody's happy, everytime sensitive-tive, the mismatched mayhem begins
アニマで制御不能
Uncontrollable by the soul
アッハッハー
Ah ha ha!
Unbiased Igy- Igy viral
Unbiased Igy- Minimanimon
恐ろしあそあそばせ
Pray, join this terrifying play
ばかりあがりまわる月に針が落ちるわ
The needle falls on the moon as it rises and spins
おちょぼ口で笑うカボチャたちと歌うわ
Singing with the pumpkins laughing with puckered lips
それが合図 魔物たちが目覚め踊るわ
That is the signal; the monsters awaken and dance
こうなればあとは思いのまま
Now that it's begun, everything is as we wish
Hollow 骨抜きダンサボ
Hollow, the bone-chilling dance floor
スケアクロウも跳び跳ねまわる
The scarecrows too are leaping around
Hollow 月夜のタンテボ
Hollow, the moonlit turntable
くるくるお静まり we gotta party night
Spinning round, quiet down, we gotta party night
Anyway, enjoy the party night
ワーワーワー 不気味なプルプル
ジャッケルクキジョ ムリムリ
Wah-wah-wah, eerie tremors
Jack-o'-lantern energy, no way, no way
背徳に洗濯はジェスなしで
夜更けのヘラヘラゲラヘルヤ
Washing away immorality without a guess
Late-night smirking, laughing, Hallelujah
What's my 素敵なナイト
見つからなくてもすでにバーナイト
What's my wonderful night?
Even if not found, it's already a bar night
雰囲気貸切 着ぐるみ島で
から早出きるりぐる
Private atmosphere on Costume Island
Making a quick getaway, dressing up
仮のショーも魂のホンモノならば魅了
Even a temporary show fascinates if the soul is real
敷き待ちなる嬢 城一両
The lady waiting, the castle's worth
サーサーサー最高に霧のリボン
Come, come, come, the ultimate misty ribbon
ガラパゴスに交わる異世界大降臨パーティー
A grand descent party of another world in Galapagos
振り切れる鼓動
The heartbeat racing past the limit
悪目な魔女のドラキュラお酒を煽るわ
The wicked witch's Dracula quaffs the liquor
寡黙そうなデュラハンも頭を振るわ
Even the silent-looking Dullahan shakes its head
紳士的なミイラスらも服がはだけるわ
Even the gentlemanly mummies have their clothes disheveled
ドあれば愉快全開のまま
With a bang, staying in full-blown delight
本性あらわに暴れよ
Reveal your true nature and run wild
その仮装も清楚になる
Even that costume becomes neat and clean
狂騒曲のタンテボ
The turntable of rhapsody
アイアイアイお静まり we gotta party night
Aye-aye-aye, quiet down, we gotta party night
Hi-Fi All night All night 眠れやしない
Hi-Fi, all night, all night, can't sleep a wink
Fly high All night All night 鳴りやまない
Fly high, all night, all night, the sound won't stop
古代も空遊び
Even in ancient times, playing in the sky
ランタンはまるで魂
The lanterns are just like souls
以前奇怪なジャンボリー
As before, a strange jamboree
闇冷えすハロウィン
A darkness-chilled Halloween
Hollow 骨抜きダンサボ
Hollow, the bone-chilling dance floor
スケアクロウも跳び跳ねまわる
The scarecrows too are leaping around
Hollow 月夜のタンテボ
Hollow, the moonlit turntable
くるくるお静まり we gotta party night
Spinning round, quiet down, we gotta party night
Anyway, enjoy the party night
くるくるお静まり we gotta party night
Spinning round, quiet down, we gotta party night
ホロウィッチの力が乱れてる。
HoloWitch's power is in disarray.
恐れと不安が解けていくんだ。
歌の力…
Fear and anxiety are melting away.
The power of song...
みんなの声の力で！
With the power of everyone's voices!
ホロウィッチのみんな、がんばれ！
いつも応援してるよ！
Go for it, everyone in HoloWitch!
I'm always rooting for you!
みんな、のってるね！
Everyone's getting into it!
ホロウィッチが力を合わせれば勝てない敵はいない！
頑張って！ホロウィッチ！
If HoloWitch joins forces, there's no enemy they can't beat!
Do your best! HoloWitch!
おかげでこっちもやる気いっぱいなのな。
Thanks to that, I'm full of motivation too.
さあ、行って。ホロウィッチ。
心を苛むトリックに…
Now, go, HoloWitch.
Against the tricks that torment the heart...
とびっきりのトリートを！
A special treat!
みんな、応援ありがとう。
Everyone, thanks for the support.
思う存分、楽しんじゃうよ！
I'm going to enjoy this to the fullest!
トリッキーに…
Tricky...
行け！
Go!
うわー、やられたー！
Whoa, we got hit!
やー！
Yah!
はー！
Hah!
イエーイ！
Yay!
イノセントバイパー！
Innocent Viper!
ラミィちゃんがんばれー！
これからの活躍に期待！
Go for it, Lamy-chan!
Looking forward to your future performance!
信じるからね。
I'm going to believe in it.
みんなの愛が、力をくれる！
Everyone's love gives me strength!
はっ！
Ha!
おりゃあ！
Oryah!
フブニャン！
Fubunyan!
ラミィちゃんナイス！
Lamy-chan, nice!
それじゃ、決めちゃうよ！
Well then, let's finish this!
はーーっ！
Haaaah!
コンッ！
Kon!
せいっ！
Sei!
ユニリアルラミネーション！
Unireal Lamination!
スラッシュ・ソンブル・コンプレッサー！
Slash Sombre Compressor!
はっ！
Ha!
えいーーやーー！
Eiiiyah!
みこみこジャンプ！
Miko-Miko Jump!
サンキューんなたん！
Thank you, Luna-tan!
そって！シークレットスフィア！
Gently! Secret Sphere!
へへっ、みんなみこのエリートなとこ、
そんなに見たいんだー。
Hehe! Does everyone want to see
Miko's elite side that much?
しょうがないねー！
I guess it can't be helped!
みんなと一緒に！
Let's go, everyone!
んなまじあるーんな！
Luna-Magial Luna!
うふふっ！
Hehe!
サイバースタジアムセイバー！
Cyber Stadium Saber!
プリンセスセイバー！
Princess Saber!
えーい！
Yah!
スプラッシュヘイロー！
Splash Halo!
はっ！
Ha!
マリン！
Marine!
てい！
Tei!
サンキューかなたん！
Thank you, Kanata!
だーっ！
Dah!
みんなの思い、全部乗っけて、
飛び込んでいくしかねーだろ！
With everyone's feelings on board,
we just have to dive in!
君たち、ちょうどいいとこに来てくれるじゃん。
You guys came right when I needed you.
みんな揃って、いいお宝ね！
All of you together make for a fine treasure!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
セレスチャルリンギング！
オーバースプラッシュベル！
Celestial Ringing!
Over Splash Bell!
あいつらでラストだ！
Those guys are the last ones!
今だよ、みんな！
It's time, everyone!
チェンジ！ホロウィッチステッキ！
Change! HoloWitch Wand!
ウィッチグラム！
Witchgram!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
ミオ先輩、もう大丈夫そう？
Mio-senpai, are you okay now?
あ、うん……
Ah, yeah...
その、見ないようにすれば、なんとか。
I can manage as long as I don't look down.
わかるよ。白上も高いとこ行くと、
下見れないからね。
I get it. Shirakami can't look down
when she's in high places either.
んなたんも、虫はなるべく見ないようにしてるのら。
Luna-tan also tries not to look at bugs
as much as possible.
ありがと、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに。
Just like you all helped me...
うちも、みんなが辛い時、苦しい時があったら……
If you're ever having a hard or painful time...
絶対、絶対に力になるから！
I'll definitely, definitely be there for you!
さて、これでめでたしめでたし。
Well, and so they lived happily ever after.
でもいいんだけど...
But that would be too simple...
みんな！
Everyone!
ホロウィッチの活躍、もっと見たいんじゃない？！
Don't you want to see more of the holoWitches in action?!
見たいー！
We want to see it!
だそうだけど...
That's what they say...
やあああ...
Ahhh...
え、こっち？こっち振るの？
Wait, me? You're passing it to me?
え、あ、や...
Wait, uh, well...
やります！
I'll do it!
よし、やるにぇ！みんな！
Alright, let's do this! Everyone!
おー！
Yeah!
RPG / 作詞：Saori, Fukase / 作曲：Fukase
RPG / Lyrics: Saori, Fukase / Composition: Fukase
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
大切な何かが
Something precious...
壊れたあの夜に
On that night when it broke
僕は星を探して
I was looking for the stars
一人で歩いていた
Walking all by myself
ペルセウス座流星群
The Perseid meteor shower
君も見てただろうか
Were you watching it too?
僕ら元気にやってるよ
We're doing just fine
君は今どこにいるの?
Where are you right now?
方法という悪魔に
By the demon called "method"
惑わされないで
Don't be led astray
目的という
Called "purpose"
大事なものを思い出して
Remember the important things
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay to be afraid
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
大切な何かが
Something precious...
壊れたあの夜に
On that night when it broke
僕は君を探して
I was looking for you
一人で歩いていた
Walking all by myself
あの日から僕らは
From that day on, we...
一人で海を目指す
Aim for the sea alone
約束のあの場所で
At that promised place
必ずまた会おうと
We'll surely meet again
世間という悪魔に
By the demon called "society"
惑わされないで
Don't be led astray
自分だけで
By yourself
決めた答えを思い出して
Remember the answer you decided on
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay to be afraid
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
煌めきのような
Like a sparkle
人生の中で
In this life
君に出会えて
Having met you
僕は本当によかった
I'm truly glad
街を抜け海に出たら
Once we leave the town and reach the sea
次はどこを目指そうか
Where shall we head next?
僕らはまた出かけよう
Let's set out again
愛おしいこの世界を
To this precious world
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖いものなんてない
There is nothing to fear
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
空は青く澄み渡り
The sky is clear and blue
海を目指して歩く
Walking towards the sea
怖くても大丈夫
It's okay even if it's scary
僕らはもう一人じゃない
We are no longer alone
みんな、今日はありがとお！
Everyone, thank you for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね、みんな！
That was the most fun Halloween ever, right everyone?
ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ、
There was a bit of an accident, but you know,
そういうのも含めて、いい思い出になったんじゃない？
including that, I think it's become a wonderful memory, don't you?
いいお宝
Great Treasure
宝
Treasure
いい思い出
Great Memory
さて、そろそろお時間となって参りましたが…
Well, it's about that time, but...
アンコール！ アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
それじゃアンコールにお答えして！
Well then, in response to your encore!
この曲、歌っちゃうのら！
We're going to sing this song!
はじまりの魔法 -charm-
The Magic of Beginnings -charm-
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
魅きいせる魔法使い
A captivating wizard
始まりを告げる
Heralding the beginning
衝動が響く
The impulse resonates
気付いた時がいつだって
Whenever you realize it
スタートラインなんだ
It's the starting line
何者でもなかった
I was nobody
君を変えたのは
What changed you was
見つけたばかりのちっぽけな
A tiny thing you just found
輝きの宝石
A jewel of radiance
どうして私だけ
Why is it just me
上手くいかないんだろう
That things don't go well for?
自分以外のすべてが
Everything other than myself
眩しく見えるけど
Looks dazzling, but
ねぇ 君に見つけて欲しくて
Hey, I want you to find me
なりたい私になる
I'll become the me I want to be
今こそ
Now is the time
空 輝きたい
I want to shine in the sky
掴みたい夢があるから
Because I have a dream I want to grasp
塞ぎ込んだ昨日言った言葉連れて
Carrying the words I said when I was down yesterday
踏み出すんだ
I'm stepping forward
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief can make a miracle happen
君に魔法をかけるよ
I'll cast a spell on you
魅きいせる魔法使い
A captivating wizard
あなたの望みと
Your wishes and
叶わない願い
Unfulfilled desires
それぞれが愛しく
Each one is precious
混ざり合っていく世界で
In a world where they mingle
何を求めて
What are you seeking
歩き続けるんだろう
As you keep walking?
いつまでもどこまでも
Forever and ever
迷うけど
I'll get lost, but
君がくれたこの空が
This sky you gave me
消えない翼を
Wings that won't disappear
くれたね
You gave them to me, didn't you?
空 照らしたい
I want to illuminate the sky
届けたい人がいるから
Because there's someone I want to reach
もう一人おいてったりしないと
I won't leave anyone behind anymore
決めたんだ
I've decided
愛したい 答えたい
I want to love, I want to respond
自分自身の火
To the fire within myself
正解なんて
Such a thing as a correct answer
これでさぁみたい君のせえ
I want to see it with this, it's because of you
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine
追いかけたいんだあの煌めきを
I want to chase that sparkle
希望 光 力 連れて
Carrying hope, light, and power
抱きしめて持っていこう
Let's embrace it and take it with us
ほら 繋げたい
Look, I want to connect
広げたい道があるから
Because there's a path I want to expand
ここから始まる物語
The story that begins from here
一緒に一歩
One step together
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
So that the power of belief can make a miracle happen
ほら
Look
飛び出して
Jump out
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
君に
To you
魔法を
Magic
かけるよ
I'll cast
We can stay oh yeah!
最高のステージだったよ、ホロウィッチ。
That was an amazing stage, holoWitches.
ほんと、ほんと！
Totally, totally!
みんな、お疲れ様。
Good job, everyone.
カノンさん、
Kanon-san,
あの、今日は本当にありがとうございました。
um, thank you so much for today.
それで、あなたはどうして、夢落ちとか僕たちのことを？
So, why do you know about Dreamfalls and us?
私、前に夢落ちして
I fell into a Dreamfall before...
君たちに助けられたことがあるんだ。
...and you girls saved me.
ええーっ！？
What!?
だから、あの時の自分と同じように
So, just like I was back then...
夢落ちして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると、放っておけなくて。
...I can't just leave someone behind when I see them suffering from a Dreamfall.
あと、実は...
Also, actually...
今日このステージに出ることにしたのも
The reason I decided to appear on this stage today...
君たちが出ると聞いたからなんだ。
...was because I heard you girls were going to be here.
もう一度会えたらって思って。
I thought I might be able to see you again.
だから今日は、えっと...
So today, um...
すごく嬉しかった！
...I was very happy!
これからも頑張ってね、ホロウィッチ。
Keep doing your best, holoWitches.
そ、それじゃあ。
W-well then.
また！ぜひまた！
See ya! For sure, see ya again!
あの人自身が夢落ちしてホロウィッチに助けられていたから
Because he was saved by holoWitches when he fell into a Dreamfall himself...
知っていたんだ。夢落ちした時の辛さも
...he knew. He knew the pain of falling into a Dreamfall...
そんな時、誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも。
...and the joy of someone reaching out their hand in a time like that.
そっか。みこたちが少しでも誰かの力になれたら
I see. If we can be even a little bit of a source of strength for someone...
その誰かが、また別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね。
...then that someone will, in turn, become a source of strength for someone else.
そうだね。しかもさ、そんだけじゃなくて
Right. And it's not just that...
うちらの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん。
...they also become a source of strength for us, don't they?
あの人や、今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに。
Like him, and everyone who supported us today.
それって...
That's...
それってすっごく...
That's super...
すっごくトリート！
...Super Treat!
キラキラ 宝石みたいに輝いてる
Sparkling, shining like a gem
夢の結晶 みんなの宝物
Crystals of dreams, everyone's treasure
時々 見失っちゃうこともあるけど
Sometimes we might lose sight of it, but...
あふれ出した 光が僕を呼ぶんだよ
...the overflowing light calls out to me
絶対 大丈夫
You'll definitely be okay
ただ まっすぐでいることも 楽じゃない日もあるよね
There are days when even just staying true to yourself isn't easy
諦めも
Giving up...
苦しみも
...and suffering...
重ねていこう 心叩き 放とう
...let's let them pile up, and then let our hearts beat and release them
夢を 歌おう
Let's sing our dreams
魔法に乗せて
Riding on magic
何度も 立ち上がる 君と一緒に進んでく
Standing up again and again, I'll keep moving forward with you
夢は 夢は まだ終わらない
Our dreams, our dreams haven't ended yet
未来を 取り戻そう
Let's take back the future
何度だって
As many times as it takes
笑って
...keep smiling...
もう一歩 歩き始めよう
...and let's start taking another step forward
ホロウィッチ
holoWitches
夢の先へ
To what lies beyond the dream
きらり光り出すんだよ
They will begin to sparkle and shine
頑張ってみても
Even if you try your best
上手くいかない日の方が
There are days when things don't go well
多く感じちゃったりするよね
And it feels like there are many of them, right?
さぁ 不安な悲しみも
Come now, don't hold onto
抱えないで 一人じゃない
Your uneasy sadness, you're not alone
希望の種を 明日に蒔いたら
If you sow the seeds of hope for tomorrow
一番に輝く 綺麗な花が咲くよ
The most beautiful flower will bloom brilliantly
夢を 歌を 魔法に乗せて
Carrying our dreams and songs on magic
何度も立ち上がる君と一緒に進んでく
I'll keep moving forward with you, as you stand up again and again
夢は 夢はまだ終わらない
The dream, the dream is not over yet
未来を取り戻そう
Let's take back the future
何度だって笑って
Smile as many times as it takes
もう一歩歩き始めよう
And let's take another step forward
ホロウィッチ！ Oh yeah! さぁ！
HoloWitch! Oh yeah! Come on!
夢の先へ
Toward the future of our dreams
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much